♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Oh, oh no, missed again.
Watch out, if the Scyphozoa pulls Aelita into the way tower,
it’s all over, we can say goodbye to the Mountain sector.
And then, bye bye Lyoko too.
We got the picture, Einstein.
Triplicate!
Impact!
Laser Arrow!
Aw…
Super sprint!
There you go, princess.
Hey, what am I, here? A groupie?
That makes twelve for me, anyone top that?
I got ten, Yumi?
Oh, not many, only fifteen.
Odd, how many of Xana’s monsters did you wipe out this week?
Two.
That’s all? What’s going on, what’s your problem?
You know darn well. You all got superpower…
telekinesis, super sprint, triplicate,
you can all make stuff appear. Me, I’ve got zilch.
The only power I ever had was future flash
and it got wiped out when Jeremy was updating the supercomputer--
--and he never reprogramed it because it was, I quote, useless.
So just knock it off with your high scores and low scores, okay?
So what did you say?
One, two, three...
He’s still sulking I guess.
Oh, I don’t believe it, is the whole world trying to bring me down or what?
Hey, look, I’m on your side.
I put a little something together that’s bound to cheer you up, Odd.
I hope it’s nothing to eat, ‘cause you’re an awful cook.
No, it’s a special power just for you and nobody else.
Teleportation.
You’re the best Einstein! If I were a girl, I’d propose to you immediately.
I’m standing by Jeremie.
This new power will allow you to travel instantly over short distances.
Cool, how does it work?
First, you have to visualize the place you want to go to, okay?
Like that big mountain for instance?
Sure, why not?
Next you activate the program by saying the word teleportation.
Okay. Teleportation.
Wow! Fantastic!
No, not fantastic at all.
Uh oh, looks like something’s bugged up.
Okay, I’ll try again
No, wait!
Teleportation.
Yoohoo! Aren’t you happy to see me?
Yeah, but honestly, one of you would have been enough.
Look up there!
Huh? What?
And there.
Jeremie, I take back my marriage proposal!
Nobody panic, it’s only a minor bug.
I’ll rematerialize you.
(MOANING)
What’s wrong?
I… I… fooled you that time, didn’t I?
Unbelievable, what a total meathead.
(MOANING)
We know, fooled us that time.
How’d you know what I was gonna say?
(MOANING)
What’s wrong, what’s going on?
Huh?
Look on the bright side,
now you’ve got two more great buddies!
That’s right!
Get real, that’s three times as many bad jokes.
And two too many Odd Della Robbia's at school.
Why don’t the two Odds lay low here to stop anyone from getting suspicious
and the other Odd can go to school as usual and everything will be cool.
Good idea. I’ll stay here and try to find out what went wrong, okay?
No way, José, it’s lunch time and we’re starved. It’s meatballs and gravy time.
Um…
What if we hid in my room and went to the lunch room one at a time?
Great idea! Nice one, Odd.
Thanks a lot guys, I thought of it, so me first, okay?
No me, I’m too hungry to wait.
Forget it, me first, I’m starved.
Stop, leave this to me, okay?
Eenie meenie, minie moe, catch a Della Robbia by the toe, you go.
Cool!
Yo Jimbo, how’s it going?
Fine, thank you Della Robbia, but watch your tone,
don’t get too familiar, the name’s Jim.
Yo Jimbo, how’s it going?
Fine, thank you Della Robbia,
but watch your tone, don’t -huh?
Hey Jimbo, how’s it going?
Uh, I’m not that great.
Actually I think I might even go lie down for a little while.
Rosa, you look beautiful today!
Have you ever thought of becoming like,
like a model or something, because you’re-
Save it, will you, Odd? I’ll give you an extra helping, just spare me the bologna.
(EATING NOISES)
Well what, I can’t keep my two best friends waiting now can I?
Yeah!
(BARKING)
Next, bon appetit!
Rosa, you look beautiful today.
Don’t push it Odd.
You already got a huge plate of meatballs.
I’ll give you some more potatoes
but that’s it, move on.
(EATING NOISES)
Yeah.
It’s your turn.
Rosa-
Alright, not another word, that’s it.
If the other kids ate as much as you do,
the lunch room would have gone under a long time ago.
Aw…
Hey, Gym class starts in five minutes. Get going.
Who’s the lucky winner?
Count me out, it’s not good exercising on a full stomach, I don’t want to be sick.
You took so many helpings that we had to go hungry!
That’s right, you selfish hog!
What me, selfish? After I wolfed down my lunch as fast as I could?
If that’s how you feel, I’m outta here.
Yeah, well, I’m going to the movies,
now that I have clones I can skip class and get away with it.
No you don’t, not so fast pal. I haven’t eaten anything,
so I’m going for takeout and you’re going to class.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, that’s my money!
No way, it’s mine!
Go on, go then, and I hope you choke on your burger!
Della Robbia, I must have seen you everywhere today.
Except in Gym class. So listen up, young man.
Get to the Gym now and work up a sweat,
or you’re gonna have something else to sweat about!
Aw…
Contrary to what some of you smart-aleks might believe, throwing a discus has nothing to do
with throwing out a CD that you’re tired of listening to.
No, it is an olympic discipline that requires strength,
skill, muscular coordination and above all, a discus.
Oh no!
Hello, what do you have in cheap movie guide magazines?
Well the cheapest one is a buck and a half. I’ve got one left.
Nothing for seventy five cents?
Uh uh.
Wheelchair Zombie 4 beginning at 2:30, great!
What do you think you’re doing?
This isn’t a public library. Hey, come back!
(PHONE RINGING)
This had better be important Jeremie.
I found out how to solve this teleportation bug problem.
The three of you each have to get into a scanner together--
--in order to fuse you back into one during the virtualization.
Okay, I get it. For once, it sounds really easy.
I wish it was, but there’s a little problem.
Your three entities are unstable.
At a certain point, all three of you could disappear into thin air, understand?
That’s horrible, what do we have to do?
Get back here to the computer lab right now, you and the terrible twins.
If any of you is missing, the fusion is impossible.
Okay, don’t worry, I’ll go find them.
A circuit in series differs from a circuit in parallel in that any single bulb
that is missing from the circuit will cut the flow of electricity.
Watch this demonstration.
Let’s put this into practice. After all, actions speak louder than words.
So here’s a demonstration for you.
Oh great, that’s all we need.
(PHONE RINGING)
Okay, Jeremie, I’m on it.
So, you bend your knees like this into a position which keeps your shifting weight in balance.
Your arm holding the discus outstretched like this.
Behind you Jim!
There’s something weird right behind you, look!
Listen up, Herb, I was not born yesterday.
What are you trying to pull?
(LAUGHING)
Now that is what I call having a hard day.
(MOANING IN TERROR)
This is Xana’s doing, let’s get to the factory.
Oh no! Help!
No!
Odd!
We have to get him out of here.
Okay, you wouldn’t happen to have a pair of wings on you?
What we’ve got to do is deactivate the tower.
If we stay here, we’ll all end up as statues.
The north entrance is still a no smoke zone.
I’ll Jeremie about Odd.
Yes, Ulrich? Petrified? Where? That means a change of plans.
(PHONE RINGING)
Jeremie? What? That’s all we need.
And what’s more, the other me isn’t in my room.
Well you’d better find him,
and then go and get number three who’s petrified on campus--
--Or else you’ll never be able to be reunited
and become one and the same.
Great idea, but how should I know where he went?
Figure it out. What would you do with your day if you were you?
Me, well I’d either go to the movies or to Presto Burger.
There you go. Now you know where to look.
ODD: Okay!
Jeremie, we’re here.
Okay, I’ll start up the virtualization.
Transfer Aelita. Transfer Yumi. Transfer Ulrich.
Scanner Aelita. Scanner Yumi. Scanner Ulrich.
Movie or Presto Burger, movie or Presto Burger, movie or Presto Burger-
Not you again! Get over here, I wanna give you a piece of my mind.
What’s that, you mean I’ve been here already?
Yeah, and if you’re planning to read another movie magazine for free,
you better think again!
You mean like this magazine here?
Yeah, you better cough up the money,
because you’re not gonna scam me again.
Surfer Zombie 4 at 2:30 at the majestic!
Hey, where you going? Get back here!
Virtualization.
I see it, the activated tower is over there.
(HUMMING)
Can’t I have two minutes on my own?
No, because we need each other’s company.
Well, they say smoking is dangerous for your health.
Better not hang around. Where’s Odd number three?
On the other side of the science building, according to Jeremie.
Okay, I guess the best way to go is up.
This is crazy, we can’t move, we’re stuck!
Hang on.
Go on, Ulrich!
Super sprint!
Aelita, watch out behind you!
He’s right down there.
Now we’ve got to bring him back.
Well if Tarzan can do it, so can we, right?
Just what I was thinking.
We’re good, pull us up!
Super sprint!
Thanks a lot!
The pleasure’s all mine.
Well what do we do now?
Hm, we have to get back to the smoke free section down there.
I’ve got an idea.
I think I just read your mind.
Go ahead the coast is clear.
Ulrich, watch out!
One, two, and, three!
(TARZAN SCREAM)
Okay, your turn!
Hey, it works!
Sure it did, what did you expect?
Better than Tarzan!
Energy field!
Super spr- ow!
It wasn’t enough that they shoot at us,
now they’re trying to run us over, that’s really not fair.
Hurry up!
Oops, sorry!
There are times when it pays to have a head as hard as a rock.
It’s between the two of you now, Aelita.
Yes, I know. And he’s pretty tough.
To think that I do everything I can to get out of gym.
About time!
Any longer and I’d have gone to the missing persons bureau!
We’re okay, Jeremie.
The Della Robbia family has been reunited.
Perfect.
Transfer Odd. Transfer Odd. Transfer Odd.
Scanner Odd. Scanner Odd. Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Well Odd?
I suddenly feel a little lonely, but that’s cool.
You’re the best Einstein.
Of course I am, did you have any doubts?
Step aside, Aelita, let an expert do the job!
Yeah!
Get ready, Aelita!
M’lady’s tower is straight ahead.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Hurry, Aelita!
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Everything okay, Jeremie?
No sweat. Just have to launch the return to the past!
I finally understood what went wrong with the teleportation process.
If you want, I could reboot the program with no bugs this time.
No thanks!
Are you sure?
Yeah, I sure am. You saw that last battle of mine,
huh? I am a top gun, a real fighting machine.
I mean, a guy like me doesn’t need special powers.
Yeah, you’re strong, very funny,
and handsome, but most of all, you’re modest.
Right, you hit the nail right on the head.
In fact, you might say that I’m one of a kind.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS